# **Sherrod Ware**

or more Web Designer/Developer - SouthCenter Red Robin

Seattle, WA 98125

kungskii88@gmail.com

12063963581

Passionate web designer, expert in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML5, CSS3,Java, Python, Web App Dev, Express Servers, and JavaScript. Creates seamless

UX and UI with creative but functional designs. Designed 8+ websites, including an ecommerce ski's sales protosite.

#readytowork

## Work Experience

### or more Web Designer/Developer

SouthCenter Red Robin - Tukwila, WA

2016 to Present

Independent website www.shareware.com/portfolio

- Rebuilt website www.artsypants.com to www.shareware.com/Artsypants2
- Independent Study website www.shareware.com/food truck
- Handled all composition, color, illustration, typography, and branding for client projects. Turned in projects an average of 5% faster than targets.

#### **Lead Line Cook and Trainer**

SouthCenter Red Robin

1994 to Present

www.red robin.com)

- Organize and prioritize client requests coming into kitchen
- Track use and order kitchen inventory
- Train newly hired employees
- Ensure efficient use of food products, labor touch points and delivery of customer orders
- Worked as a team member in a high stress fast paced environment
- Self motivated able to perform with little or no supervision

## or more Project Manager prerequisite for AAS Degree

#### SouthCenter Red Robin

June 2017 to September 2017

Front End Web Designer/Developer

- Send emails to clients and respond to incoming emails
- Ensured that all projects were delivered on-time
- Assisted with the overall design and logo of project
- Created custom graphics sets for clients, with 99% client satisfaction scores.

## Education

## **Bachelor's in Application Development**

North Seattle College - Seattle, WA

April 2019 to Present

## Web Design Certificate in IT Web Design

Seattle Central College - Seattle, WA

April 2014 to Present

## Skills

•

• ILLUSTRATOR (5 years)

•

WEB DESIGN

•

WORDPRESS (2 years)

•

• DREAMWEAVER (5 years)

•

HTML5 (5 years)

•

Photoshop (5 years)

•

Javascript (5 years)

•

Website (6 years)

Wireframe (6 years) PHP (5 years) Android (3 years) MYSQL (3 years) CSS (5 years) Git (3 years) HTML 5 (5 years) Java (3 years) APIs (3 years) User Interface (UI)  $\mathsf{XML}$ APIs (3 years) User Experience (UX) (5 years) Web Development (5 years) User Interface (UI) (5 years) GitHub (5 years)

Front-End Development (5 years)

,

•	Test Cases (3 years)
•	Application Development (3 years)
•	Bootstrap (5 years)
•	Microsoft SQL Server (1 year)
•	React.js (3 years)
•	Node.js (3 years)
•	SQL (2 years)
•	NGINX (2 years)
•	Web services (5 years)
•	React Native (3 years)
•	REST (2 years)
•	MongoDB (1 year)
•	AWS (2 years)
•	React (2 years)
•	React Native
•	Python 3 (3 years)
_	

•

Expo (2 years)

•	iOS (3 years)
•	Computer science
•	Figma (3 years)
•	Web accessibility (5 years)
•	Usability (5 years)
•	Responsive web design (5 years)
•	Workday (8 years)
•	SaaS (3 years)
•	Graphic design (5 years)
•	UI design (5 years)
•	Statistical analysis (3 years)
•	Layout design (5 years)
•	Visual design (5 years)
•	Software Development (5 years)
Languages	
	English - Fluent
Link	KS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sherrod-ware-407545145/ https://www.sherrodware.com/foodtruck https://www.sherrodware.com/portfolio Certifications and Licenses food handler certificate ServSafe Assessments Search Engine Optimization — Familiar April 2020 Interpreting online website performance metrics and understanding search engine optimization tactics Full results: **Familiar** Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field. Additional Information Skills Languages • Expert with HTML5, CSS3/Sass/SCSS, JavaScript, JQuery, to handle 95% of projects • Gathered all project requirements with 95% fidelity to project needs. Software • Expert with Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Dreamweaver, with · Microsoft Office, WordPress **Tools** 

• Expert with Adobe Brackets, Filezilla, to handle all web design for 95% of projects.

• Worked with PHPMyAdmin, Cloud9